all right coming up next a matchup to
determine the baddest man on the planet
the ufc heavyweight title is on the line
well for a long time he's been mentioned
with the baddest man on the planet for a
long time though
the title fight eluded him not anymore
here he is the number one heavyweight
contender
finally making this walk and cracking
the smile he's waited a long time for
this
he's not expecting a 25-minute war he
believes he has the power and the skills
to get this thing done quickly i guess
we'll find out
[Applause]
[Music]
well a lot of people think it's the most
significant title in combat sports no
argument from me
baddest man on the planet ufc
heavyweight champion
there he is in the flesh what an
absolute monster
what a title reign it has been but a
serious challenge in front of him here
tonight when this man
became the heavyweight champion a lot of
people thought that this challenger was
the one who would rest the belt away
now the fight is here we'll see if we
get a new champion
or if this man continues one of the
greatest heavyweight legacies
the octagon has ever seen
[Applause]
our tale of the tape for this
heavyweight championship fight
both fighters identical in age with big
differences in height
and reach and now to get us started
here's bruce buff
ladies and gentlemen this is the
belt of the evening and when the action
begins our referee in charge of the
octagon
eve loving and
now this is the moment
ufc fans around the world have been
waiting for
live from the sold out madison square
garden arena
in new york city
the undisputed usc
heavyweight championship of the world
introducing first fighting out of the
blue corners
this man is a boxer making his
professional debut here tonight
he stands six feet six inches tall
weighing in at 265 pounds
fighting out of the republic of dagestan
russia
presenting the challenger
monster
[Applause]
this man is a kickboxer making his
professional debut here tonight
he stands five feet seven inches tall
weighing in at 135 pounds
fighting out of shanghai china
presenting
the reigning defending
undisputed ufc
heavyweight champion of the world
ufc belt online protect yourself at all
times we'll bring my command at all time
if you want to touch love do it now i'll
go back to your corner they touch them
up and we are underway
all right so two truly elite strikers
here we sat down with them on thursday
and asked them
any thoughts of taking this fight to the
ground they want to strike they want to
strike that's what got them to show
that is the path that they are normally
on
and tonight they get someone that allows
them to fight in their comfort zone
they don't have to worry about defending
takedowns all they have to worry about
is she can rely on their knowledge in
the striking
to carry this victory oh really
exploiting his reach advantage as he
landed the jab there dc
big kick
[Applause]
all right he engages in the single
collar tie
oh tagged him with that right hand what
a strike that looks
what a strike that he is landing over
and over again his opponent will need to
make some adjustments
throwing that jab yet again out of range
that comes from him
[Applause]
oh superman punch is good you can tell
he's been working on that
well perhaps a sign of things to come as
he lands a kick there nice kick
landed by this gentleman and they settle
big ball from the first land now we get
back stuff to take down no problem
big power shot there
[Music]
oh big superman punch there
alright he closes the distance gets the
single collar tie
oh nice connection there with the punch
dc great time
to land that one and they separate
there's the kick it's blocked
well he absorbs a kick to the head here
left it wide open he's got to not move
into that power shot let's see if he can
[Applause]
adjust
dc i know you can't necessarily relate
oh man you jumped out of your seat a
little bit after that
oh i did because i have time where i've
been kicked like that and i'm gonna tell
you
one thing it does not feel good
all right so a good job defensively by
him here as he raises the guard and
prevents any damage shades of james
tony always seeing things coming out it
was such a great defensive fighter
[Applause]
big punch lands over the top how's he
gonna follow this one
so there it is longer reach paying
dividends as he counters with a punch
[Applause]
well he's got the kicking game going
tonight lands another one there a
beautiful kick and all i can think of
better him
than me stuffs the take down there how
good is his takedown defense
oh caller tie oh really using his reach
advantage
maybe time to get the bonus checks ready
i mean this fight is about
done he's got it very bad now he has to
find one more strike
to end the night oh no way spinning back
fist
he went high on that one
they continue to exchange
[Applause]
just misses with the jet
oh you got to be kidding me another head
kick lands
he's got to start blocking these dc one
more and it could be lights out
it could be over and most people would
be sleeping on the mat
after taking such a dominant strike
credit to his chin
but you don't want to get kicked that
many times in the head all right single
caller tie now
big knee land lee gets hit by that kick
to the midsection you got to do better
defensively
boom big shot wins
let's get there to the body
five minutes in the books
well what around it was and how about
that flying superman punch at the end of
the round
not a lot of fighters will try it he did
he executed and it worked
right no discouragement from his
opponent to make him not try it
why not try it it's working so why not
try it again
if his opponent isn't careful he will
get knocked out and be on the highlight
reel
for the rest of the time second round
underway
nice kick right there tell the masses
how good that feels
it doesn't feel good
continues to mix it up going to the head
mixing in some body shots
oh nice
we're going at it now
[Applause]
lands a big right hand knee to the body
oh body kick attempt here it's no good
oh
that is
well he has landed some good shots dc
but really unable to string anything
together in terms of solid combination
it's because he's not committing to it
fully he throws his jab
how's his opponent still standing i mean
i have no idea
this fight is supposed to be over it
might not be over now
but it's going to be over very soon
[Applause]
and he landed the right hand there
oh superman punch
back to the well with that right hand
it's no good
look at him
[Applause]
oh nice job to land the straight punch
there must be nice to have that kind of
reach advantage dc i know you can't
necessarily relate oh nice job to win
the knee upstairs there that's going to
leave a mark and again we talk about the
size advantage
we certainly put it to good use there
[Applause]
well a really good second round for him
thus far after a somewhat lackluster
first round he
found the rhythm and found his striking
range scary proposition for the opponent
now
here in round two
[Applause]
[Music]
oh and a nice jab by him there and
that's going to give his opponent some
problems if that keeps landing
he's having a tough
[Applause]
you don't really stand after you take a
head hit like this
that is such a toughness to even be on
his feet right now
on to him here not really doing too much
perhaps just looking to recover
[Applause]
i know you don't often have the reach
advantage but nice to see him making
good use of it in this matchup
clean with the rifle
just missed with the left there
[Applause]
very badly when he comes
needs another huge knee
[Applause]
right hook to the head block
oh he just continues to pour it on he
has been aggressive
all night long with his striking gotta
be careful here
to not empty the gas tank so far so good
though in this round
oh
10 seconds to go in the round
nice body kit
all right that's the end of round number
two oh the round is over and blood is
just fauceting out of his cheek that
cheek has gotten out of control
cut man can only do so much and given
the fact that that cut continues to be
attacked by
the opponent if this thing gets any
worse they're gonna stop this fight
all right let's now look back at some of
the action from that round he went head
hunting
landed nearly got the finish too a lot
of coaches tell you don't head hunt
in this case he's been head hunting and
he landed a big enough shot
to truly put his opponent on notice
[Applause]
you ready you ready here we go
third round of this championship fight
straight right he misses great punch
well just as he did in the previous
round he continues to connect on a high
volume of strikes
and a good sign too doesn't seem to be
slowing down whatsoever
looking to land the right hand he misses
[Applause]
nice one two there
single collar tie now
big punches
he's just too good in this position look
for ground and pound immediately
posturing up now and now the damage is
about to start
alright he's very comfortable fighting
off his back dc now looks like he's
trying to hip escape
yeah he's trying to hip escape or maybe
look for kimura here
beautiful movement hip work on the
ground here just outstanding with the
transition he is not staying in one
place on the ground and that's very
important
[Applause]
throwing that jab now again the fighter
of eights
stuffs that take down attempts without
issue nice punch there by lee
and both guys really throwing with
authority
just over three minutes to go in round
three
[Applause]
oh he lands another strike to the body
really starting to connect on a lot of
shots to the midsection
and these will take their toll as this
fight goes into the latter rounds
oh he goes to the counter right just out
of range
[Applause]
oh straight right
how about that shin forget him
into that
[Applause]
nice job by him to get the need and the
target there using his length
exceptionally well tonight
oh continuing to work the body to great
effect
lands a good series of kicks there dc it
really didn't take him long to get a
good beat on his opponent
he figured the timing and now he's been
driving kick after kick
into his opponent
[Applause]
able to land to the body there with the
left kick
try to establish that jab
[Applause]
oh we'll see if he can finish
big knee lands there
[Applause]
well not sure if he's lighter on his
feet or what it is but these last couple
of rounds
he's been far more aggressive a lot more
pressure oh he's really starting to
light him up now
[Applause]
another shot like that look at him whip
his hip
into that kick all right let's go
just misses there with the left
a little single collar tie there glad to
switch these
[Applause]
seconds winding down in round three
all right the round is over gut check
time for him now you see the cut on his
cheek has gotten really really bad and
even though it's not affecting his
vision
if it gets any worse the doctor will be
called in and i can assure you
he's gonna have no choice but to stop
this fight all right so there's the end
of the round and the tide has officially
turned a huge head strike to stun his
opponent we'll see which corner can
adjust here moving forward
i mean they've got to be celebrated
they've got to be happy everything's
working
but the other side has to be concerned
they have to figure
something out make some sort of
adjustment to try to change the tide
of this fight all right so here we go
with our fourth round of a possible five
and a lot of fighters change up their
training camp when they're fighting five
rounds versus three
yeah you gotta change it up you have to
mix things up because fighting for an
extra
is not normal guys don't do this
normally it's a 15-minute fight
so you have to do things physically and
also mentally
to make sure that you're ready to go to
the next pitman
[Applause]
well he hasn't really showed any signs
of slowing down tonight he continues to
connect
on a high volume of strikes here
nice punch lands over the top
[Applause]
nice
obvious redness on the right side of his
body
lee gets caught by that straight punch
his defense has abandoned him tonight
and they separate and now he's got that
tie
clinch we'll see what he can do with it
all right
gage is going to see the color tie here
right on the button
that is
it's like tom brady out there he hasn't
missed the target i mean you insist on
bringing in tom brady stop it
well he continues to find the openings
tonight beautiful connection with the
punch there
accuracy at its best oh good opportunity
to do damage here he's got that tie
clinch
spinning back this oh big knee
[Applause]
well you didn't see a lot of the
bodywork from him in the earlier rounds
but he's certainly getting after it here
big shot to the body connects there
we'll see if he can follow it up that
one appeared to stun him
he's hurt he's not impressive he's got
to go chase that finish down though
[Applause]
oh
he's got a serious right punch and he
went to it effectively there it is his
money shot and he will continue to throw
it
[Applause]
just over two minutes to go
oh huge bluff look at how he turned his
hip
into that leg kick lee gets caught with
that push
oh he lands the superman punch
[Applause]
he needs to start looking to finish now
because he's got his opponent hurt very
bad
trying to get the knees going
[Applause]
nice kick
oh he might be out
[Applause]
lee's shot
[Music]
tried to go to the body but unable to
connect
he connects with the punch there dc you
like this guys i like this guy a ton
and to watch his punch like this puts a
smile on my face
and he got the kick we'll see what he
can do with him
dc now we'll see if he can follow it up
when you throw a hook it can go around
the guard
of your opponent over and over he's
landing a big body kick
oh strong hook to the head there by lee
really timing his shots nicely good
tempo very accurate finding the range
with relative ease
yeah he's doing a great job of really
overwhelming his opponent with
activities
all right so a huge round for him there
nearly had him out of there with the
head kick did get the knock down
talk us through the replay he got the
knock down he won the round
he did everything correct the only thing
he didn't do is finish the fight
but if he continues down the path if he
continues to do the exact same thing as
he did before
he will get that finish
[Applause]
you ready you ready it is the fifth
and final round
[Applause]
way to hide that leg kick
right punches there
right hand on point
[Applause]
big punch lands through the middle
what a tricky head kick
look at him working at trying to shut
the liver down
[Applause]
splits the guard lands the right hand oh
stuffs the takedown without issue
changes his stance you'll see a lot of
this from this fighter
all right so a nice job there
defensively to raise the guard and
prevent any damage
those hands never leave where they're
supposed to be and if you do that
most times you will block the shot
that's income
gets caught with that punch what a body
kick
[Applause]
oh crippling knee to the body
just over three minutes now to go in the
fight
all right so he lands a jab there pretty
nicely done dc you can really control
the fight
just knowing how to fight fight oh what
a shot to the body he's going to attack
that region
mission accomplished mission
accomplished it does not get much better
than that
well body language
[Applause]
he's as confused as he was
[Music]
it is very difficult
[Applause]
i should say so a tremendous kick to end
that fight tonight
caught his opponent flush full force
full extension
and he had no chance to stay in this
fight fight was over as soon as that
kick made flush contact well he's going
to enjoy watching this one back let's
take a look at the replay of the
knockout just a moment ago it was right
hand after right hand after right hand
finally he found the one that hit the
exact sweet spot
that ended his opponent's night
we send it inside now to bruce buffer
for the official decision
ladies and gentlemen referee eve levine
has called to stop with this contest
at two minutes 52 seconds of cloud
number five
and still
[Applause]
and still the baddest man on the planet
i know you haven't retired yet but uh i
don't necessarily want to see you share
the octagon with that one
i mean this dude is a savage there is
prestige in being called the ufc
heavyweight champion
he remains